Guide to the Newspaper Guild of New York Records WAG.125
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
- Series II: Early Records: Shop Files, 1935-1950
  - World Telegram: Correspondence, 1939-1941 (Box 63, Folder 1)
  - World Telegram: Correspondence, 1942-1946 (Box 63, Folder 2)
  - World Telegram: Correspondence, 1943-1944 (Box 63, Folder 3)
  - World Telegram: Correspondence, 1943-1945 (Box 63, Folder 4)
  - World Telegram: Correspondence, 1946 (Box 63, Folder 5)
  - World Telegram: Correspondence, 1946 (Box 63, Folder 6)
  - World Telegram: Correspondence, 1947 (Box 63, Folder 7)
  - World Telegram: Correspondence, 1947 (Box 63, Folder 8)
  - World Telegram: Correspondence, 1948 (Box 63, Folder 9)
  - World Telegram: Correspondence, 1948 (Box 63, Folder 10)
  - World Telegram: Correspondence, 1948-1949 (Box 63, Folder 11)
  - World Telegram: Correspondence, 1949 (Box 63, Folder 12)
  - World Telegram: Correspondence, 1950 (Box 63, Folder 13)
  - World Telegram: Correspondence, 1950 (Box 63, Folder 14)
  - World Telegram: Correspondence, 1950 (Box 63, Folder 15)
  - World Telegram: Negotiations, 1937-1938 (Box 63, Folder 16)
  - World Telegram: Negotiations I, 1939 (Box 63, Folder 17)
  - World Telegram: Negotiations II, 1939 (Box 63, Folder 18)
  - World Telegram: Negotiations III, 1939 (Box 63, Folder 19)
  - World Telegram: Negotiations IV, 1939 (Box 63, Folder 20)
  - World Telegram: Negotiations V, 1939 (Box 63, Folder 21)
  - World Telegram: Negotiations VI, 1939 (Box 63, Folder 22)
  - World Telegram: Negotiations VII, 1939 (Box 63, Folder 23)
  - World Telegram: Negotiations, 1939-1940 (Box 63, Folder 24)
  - World Telegram: Negotiations, 1940 (Box 63, Folder 25)
  - World Telegram: Negotiations, 1940-1941 (Box 63, Folder 26)
  - World Telegram: Negotiations, 1941 (Box 63, Folder 27)
  - World Telegram: Negotiations, 1943 (Box 63, Folder 28)
  - World Telegram: Negotiations, 1943 (Box 63, Folder 29)
  - World Telegram: Negotiations, 1943-1944 (Box 63, Folder 30)
  - World Telegram: Negotiations, 1944 (Box 63, Folder 31)
  - World Telegram: Negotiations, 1944 (Box 63, Folder 32)
  - World Telegram: Negotiations, 1944-1945 (Box 63, Folder 33)
  - World Telegram: Negotiations, 1945 (Box 63, Folder 34)
  - World Telegram: Negotiations, 1945 (Box 63, Folder 35)
  - World Telegram: Negotiations, 1945 (Box 63, Folder 36)
  - World Telegram: Negotiations, 1945-1946 (Box 63, Folder 37)
  - World Telegram: Negotiations, 1946 (Box 63, Folder 38)
  - World Telegram: Negotiations, 1946 (Box 64, Folder 1)
  - World Telegram: Negotiations, 1946 (Box 64, Folder 2)
  - World Telegram: Negotiations, 1946 (Box 64, Folder 3)
  - World Telegram: Negotiations, 1946-1947 (Box 64, Folder 4)
  - World Telegram: Negotiations, 1947 (Box 64, Folder 5)
  - World Telegram: Negotiations, 1947 (Box 64, Folder 6)
  - World Telegram: Negotiations, 1947 (Box 64, Folder 7)
  - World Telegram: Negotiations, 1948 (Box 64, Folder 8)
  - World Telegram: Negotiations, 1948 (Box 64, Folder 9)
  - World Telegram: Negotiations, 1948 (Box 64, Folder 10)
  - World Telegram: Negotiations, 1949 (Box 64, Folder 11)
  - World Telegram: Negotiations, 1949 (Box 64, Folder 12)
  - World Telegram: Negotiations, 1949 (Box 64, Folder 13)
  - World Telegram: Negotiations, 1950 (Box 64, Folder 14)
  - World Telegram: Negotiations, 1950 (Box 64, Folder 15)
  - World Telegram: Negotiations, 1950 (Box 64, Folder 16)
  - World Telegram: Grievances, 1940 (Box 64, Folder 17)
  - World Telegram: Grievances, 1941 (Box 64, Folder 18)
  - World Telegram: Grievances I, 1943-1944 (Box 64, Folder 19)
  - World Telegram: Grievances II, 1943-1944 (Box 64, Folder 20)
  - World Telegram: Grievances, 1944 (Box 64, Folder 21)
  - World Telegram: Grievances, 1944 (Box 64, Folder 22)
  - World Telegram: Grievances, 1946 (Box 64, Folder 23)
  - World Telegram: Grievances, 1947 (Box 64, Folder 24)
  - World Telegram: Grievances, 1947 (Box 64, Folder 25)
  - World Telegram: Grievances, 1948 (Box 64, Folder 26)
  - World Telegram: Shop Papers, 1937-1950 (Box 64, Folder 27)
  - World Telegram: Contracts, 1937-1950 (Box 64, Folder 28)
  - World Telegram: Leaflets, 1937-1950 (Box 64, Folder 29)
- Series III: General Files, 1951-1998
  Series III: General Files, 1951-1998, contains correspondence, committee files, officers' files, election files, convention records, publications, and subject files.
  - Administrative Committee, 1951-1952 (Box 65, Folder 1)
  - Administrative Committee, 1953-1954 (Box 65, Folder 2)
  - Administrative Committee, 1955-1957 (Box 65, Folder 3)
  - Administrative Committee, 1958-1959 (Box 65, Folder 4)
  - Administrative Committee, 1960-1961 (Box 65, Folder 5)
  - Administrative Committee, 1962-1963 (Box 65a, Folder 1)
  - Administrative Committee, 1964-1965 (Box 65a, Folder 2)
  - Administrative Committee, 1966-1967 (Box 65a, Folder 3)
  - Administrative Committee, 1968-1969 (Box 65a, Folder 4)
  - Administrative Committee, 1970-1971 (Box 65a, Folder 5)
  - Administrative Committee, 1973-1975 (Box 65a, Folder 6)
  - Administrative Committee, 1977-1980 (Box 65a, Folder 7)
  - Administrative Committee, 1981-1989 (Box 65a, Folder 8)
  - Administrative Pension Committee, 1968 (Box 65a, Folder 9)
  - Advertising Lineage, 1951-1952 (Box 65a, Folder 10)
  - Affirmative Action, 1974; 1981-1987 (Box 66, Folder 1)
  - African-American Labor Center, 1980 (Box 66, Folder 2)
  - Alcoholism, 1977; 1982 (Box 66, Folder 3)
  - Allied Printing and Trades Council (City and State), 1959-1961 (Box 66, Folder 4)
  - Allied Printing and Trades Council (City and State), 1962 (Box 66, Folder 5)
  - Allied Printing and Trades Council (City and State), 1963-1969 (Box 66, Folder 6)
  - Allied Printing and Trades Council (City and State), 1970-1977 (Box 66, Folder 7)
  - Allied Printing and Trades Council (City and State), 1978-1982 (Box 66, Folder 8)
  - Allied Printing and Trades Council (City and State), 1983-1991 (Box 66, Folder 9)
  - Allied Unity Committee (Photo), 1963-1964 (Box 66, Folder 10)
  - Amalgamated Bank of New York, 1950-1952; 1973; 1980s (Box 66, Folder 11)
  - American Arbitrations Association, 1965-1989 (Box 66, Folder 12)
  - American Broadcasting Company (ABC), 1967 (Box 66, Folder 13)
  - American Committee to Keep Biafra Alive, 1968 (Box 66, Folder 14)
  - American Federation of Labor-Congress of Industrial Organizations (AFL-CIO), 1955-1959 (Box 66, Folder 15)
  - American Federation of Labor-Congress of Industrial Organizations, 1960 (Box 66, Folder 16)
  - American Federation of Labor-Congress of Industrial Organizations, 1961 (Box 66, Folder 17)
  - American Federation of Labor-Congress of Industrial Organizations, 1962-1964 (Box 67, Folder 1)
  - American Federation of Labor-Congress of Industrial Organizations, 1965-1969 (Box 67, Folder 2)
  - American Federation of Labor-Congress of Industrial Organizations, 1970-1972 (Box 67, Folder 3)
  - American Federation of Labor-Congress of Industrial Organizations, 1973-1974 (Box 67, Folder 4)
  - American Federation of Labor-Congress of Industrial Organizations, 1975-1978 (Box 67, Folder 5)
  - American Federation of Labor-Congress of Industrial Organizations, 1985-1988 (Box 67, Folder 6)
  - AFL-CIO: Committee on Political Education (COPE), 1950s (Box 67, Folder 7)
  - AFL-CIO: Committee on Political Education, 1960s (Box 67, Folder 8)
  - AFL-CIO: Committee on Political Education, 1970s (Box 67, Folder 9)
  - AFL-CIO: Committee on Political Education, 1980s (Box 67, Folder 10)
  - AFL-CIO: COPE (John F. Kennedy), 1960s (Box 67, Folder 11)
  - AFL-CIO: New York City Central Labor Council, 1961; 1965-1966 (Box 67, Folder 12)
  - AFL-CIO: Merger, 1956-1957 (Box 67, Folder 13)
  - AFL-CIO: Unity Pact, 1955 (Box 67, Folder 14)
  - American Federation of Television and Radio Artists, 1967; 1982 (Box 67, Folder 15)
  - American Guild of Variety Artists, 1982 (Box 67, Folder 16)
  - American Newspaper Guild, 1951 (Box 67, Folder 17)
  - American Newspaper Guild, 1952 (Box 67, Folder 18)
  - American Newspaper Guild, 1953-1956 (Box 67, Folder 19)
  - American Newspaper Guild, 1957 (Box 67, Folder 20)
  - American Newspaper Guild, 1958 (Box 67, Folder 21)
  - American Newspaper Guild, 1959 (Box 67, Folder 22)
  - American Newspaper Guild, 1960 (Box 67, Folder 23)
  - American Newspaper Guild, 1961 (Box 67, Folder 24)
  - American Newspaper Guild, 1962 (Box 68, Folder 1)
  - American Newspaper Guild, 1963 (Box 68, Folder 2)
  - American Newspaper Guild, 1964 (Box 68, Folder 3)
  - American Newspaper Guild, 1965 (Box 68, Folder 4)
  - American Newspaper Guild, 1966 (Box 68, Folder 5)
  - American Newspaper Guild, 1967 (Box 68, Folder 6)
  - American Newspaper Guild, 1968 (Box 68, Folder 7)
  - American Newspaper Guild, 1969 (Box 68, Folder 8)
  - American Newspaper Guild, 1970 (Box 68, Folder 9)
  - American Newspaper Guild, 1971 (Box 68, Folder 10)
  - American Newspaper Guild: Age Discrimination, 1968-1971 (Box 68, Folder 11)
  - American Newspaper Guild: Anti-Trust Activity, 1969 (Box 68, Folder 12)
  - American Newspaper Guild: Arbitrations Awards, 1951 (Box 68, Folder 13)
  - American Newspaper Guild: Arbitrations Reports, 1958-1965 (Box 68, Folder 14)
  - American Newspaper Guild: Assessments, 1971 (Box 68, Folder 15)
  - American Newspaper Guild: Assessments (Defense Fund), 1963 (Box 68, Folder 16)
  - American Newspaper Guild: Assessments (Dues Increase), 1966 (Box 68, Folder 17)
  - American Newspaper Guild: Assessment Petitions, 1969 (Box 68, Folder 18)
  - American Newspaper Guild: Assessment Referendum (I), 1968 (Box 68, Folder 19)
  - American Newspaper Guild: Assessment Referendum (II), 1968 (Box 68, Folder 20)
  - American Newspaper Guild: Assessment Referendum, 1969 (Box 69, Folder 1)
  - American Newspaper Guild: Assessment Schedule, 1966; 1970 (Box 69, Folder 2)
  - American Newspaper Guild: Assessment Termination, 1964 (Box 69, Folder 3)
  - American Newspaper Guild: Audits General, 1971 (Box 69, Folder 4)
  - American Newspaper Guild: Beaumont, Texas Matter, 1957 (Box 69, Folder 5)
  - American Newspaper Guild: Brooklyn Eagle Unit, 1956 (Box 69, Folder 6)
  - American Newspaper Guild: Committee Chairmen, 1960 (Box 69, Folder 7)
  - American Newspaper Guild: Computerized Bookkeeping Conversion, 1971 (Box 69, Folder 8)
  - American Newspaper Guild: Constitution, 1971 (Box 69, Folder 9)
  - American Newspaper Guild: Continuing Collective Bargaining Committee, 1953 (Box 69, Folder 10)
  - American Newspaper Guild: Contracts, 1953-1954 (Box 69, Folder 11)
  - American Newspaper Guild Convention (I), 1951 (Box 69, Folder 12)
  - American Newspaper Guild Convention (II), 1951 (Box 69, Folder 13)
  - American Newspaper Guild Convention, 1952 (Box 69, Folder 14)
  - American Newspaper Guild Convention, 1953 (Box 69, Folder 15)
  - American Newspaper Guild Convention, 1954 (Box 69, Folder 16)
  - American Newspaper Guild Convention (I), 1955 (Box 70, Folder 1)
  - American Newspaper Guild Convention (II), 1955 (Box 70, Folder 2)
  - American Newspaper Guild Convention (I), 1956 (Box 70, Folder 3)
  - American Newspaper Guild Convention (II), 1956 (Box 70, Folder 4)
  - American Newspaper Guild Convention, 1957 (Box 70, Folder 5)
  - American Newspaper Guild Convention (I), 1958 (Box 70, Folder 6)
  - American Newspaper Guild Convention (II), 1958 (Box 70, Folder 7)
  - American Newspaper Guild Convention (I), 1959 (Box 70, Folder 8)
  - American Newspaper Guild Convention (II), 1959 (Box 70, Folder 9)
  - American Newspaper Guild Convention (III), 1959 (Box 70, Folder 10)
  - American Newspaper Guild Convention, 1960 (Box 70, Folder 11)
  - American Newspaper Guild Convention: Delegates and Alternates, 1960 (Box 70, Folder 12)
  - American Newspaper Guild Convention, 1961 (Box 71, Folder 1)
  - American Newspaper Guild Convention: Delegates and Alternates, 1961 (Box 71, Folder 2)
  - American Newspaper Guild Convention, 1962 (Box 71, Folder 3)
  - American Newspaper Guild Convention, 1963 (Box 71, Folder 4)
  - American Newspaper Guild Convention, 1964 (Box 71, Folder 5)
  - American Newspaper Guild Convention, 1965 (Box 71, Folder 6)
  - American Newspaper Guild Convention, 1966 (Box 71, Folder 7)
  - American Newspaper Guild Convention, 1967 (Box 71, Folder 8)
  - American Newspaper Guild Convention, 1968 (Box 71, Folder 9)
  - American Newspaper Guild Convention (I), 1969 (Box 71, Folder 10)
  - American Newspaper Guild Convention (II), 1969 (Box 71, Folder 11)
  - American Newspaper Guild Convention, 1970 (Box 72, Folder 1)
  - American Newspaper Guild Convention, 1971 (Box 72, Folder 2)
  - American Newspaper Guild Convention: Delegates; Acceptances and Declines, 1983 (Box 72, Folder 3)
  - American Newspaper Guild: Defense Fund Buffalo Referendum, 1964 (Box 72, Folder 4)
  - American Newspaper Guild: Election of International Vice-Presidents, 1957-1965 (Box 72, Folder 5)
  - American Newspaper Guild: Election Rules, 1971 (Box 72, Folder 6)
  - American Newspaper Guild: Finance, 1970-1974 (Box 72, Folder 7)
  - American Newspaper Guild: Guild Service Award, 1971; 1976 (Box 72, Folder 8)
  - American Newspaper Guild: Health and Welfare Conference, 1954; 1958 (Box 72, Folder 9)
  - American Newspaper Guild: Hearst Suit, 1956-1959 (Box 72, Folder 10)
  - American Newspaper Guild: Human Rights, 1954-1969 (Box 72, Folder 11)
  - American Newspaper Guild: Insurance, 1956; 1971 (Box 72, Folder 12)
  - American Newspaper Guild: Internal Revenue Code, 1955 (Box 72, Folder 13)
  - American Newspaper Guild: International Executive Board, 1951 (Box 72, Folder 14)
  - American Newspaper Guild: International Executive Board, 1952 (Box 72, Folder 15)
  - American Newspaper Guild: International Executive Board, 1953 (Box 72, Folder 16)
  - American Newspaper Guild: International Executive Board, 1954 (Box 72, Folder 17)
  - American Newspaper Guild: International Executive Board, 1955-1956 (Box 72, Folder 18)
  - American Newspaper Guild: International Executive Board, 1957 (Box 72, Folder 19)
  - American Newspaper Guild: International Executive Board, 1958 (Box 72, Folder 20)
  - American Newspaper Guild: International Executive Board, 1959 (Box 72, Folder 21)
  - American Newspaper Guild: International Executive Board, 1960 (Box 73, Folder 1)
  - American Newspaper Guild: International Executive Board, 1961 (Box 73, Folder 2)
  - American Newspaper Guild: International Executive Board, 1962 (Box 73, Folder 3)
  - American Newspaper Guild: International Executive Board, 1963 (Box 73, Folder 4)
  - American Newspaper Guild: International Executive Board, 1964 (Box 73, Folder 5)
  - American Newspaper Guild: International Executive Board, 1965 (Box 73, Folder 6)
  - American Newspaper Guild: International Executive Board, 1966 (Box 73, Folder 7)
  - American Newspaper Guild: International Executive Board, 1967 (Box 73, Folder 8)
  - American Newspaper Guild: International Executive Board, 1969 (Box 73, Folder 9)
  - American Newspaper Guild: International Executive Board, 1970 (Box 73, Folder 10)
  - American Newspaper Guild: International Executive Board, 1971-1974 (Box 73, Folder 11)
  - American Newspaper Guild: International Executive Board, 1975-1976 (Box 73, Folder 12)
  - American Newspaper Guild: International Executive Board, 1977-1982 (Box 73, Folder 13)
  - American Newspaper Guild: International Press Cards, 1971 (Box 73, Folder 14)
  - American Newspaper Guild: Leadership Training Conference, 1951 (Box 73, Folder 15)
  - American Newspaper Guild: Local Agreements, 1962 (Box 73, Folder 16)
  - American Newspaper Guild: Local Agreements, 1969-1973 (Box 73, Folder 17)
  - American Newspaper Guild: Locals, Organizing and Servicing Program, 1971 (Box 73, Folder 18)
  - American Newspaper Guild: Mail Ballot difficulties, 1969-1971 (Box 73, Folder 19)
  - American Newspaper Guild: Mail Ballots, 1960 (Box 73, Folder 20)
  - American Newspaper Guild: Membership (Locals), 1954-1957 (Box 73, Folder 21)
  - American Newspaper Guild: Membership (Locals), 1967 (Box 73, Folder 22)
  - American Newspaper Guild: Membership (Locals), 1968 (Box 73, Folder 23)
  - American Newspaper Guild: Membership and Statistics (Locals), 1951-1953 (Box 74, Folder 1)
  - American Newspaper Guild: Membership and Statistics (Locals), 1958-1961 (Box 74, Folder 2)
  - American Newspaper Guild: Membership and Statistics (Locals), 1962-1966 (Box 74, Folder 3)
  - American Newspaper Guild: Membership and Statistics (Locals), 1969-1971 (Box 74, Folder 4)
  - American Newspaper Guild: Minority Groups Recruitment and Training Conference, 1971 (Box 74, Folder 5)
  - American Newspaper Guild: Minority Roots Conference, 1971 (Box 74, Folder 6)
  - American Newspaper Guild: Monopoly in Newspaper Industry, 1955 (Box 74, Folder 7)
  - American Newspaper Guild: Out of Town Locals, 1951-1953 (Box 74, Folder 8)
  - American Newspaper Guild: Out of Town Locals, 1954-1956 (Box 74, Folder 9)
  - American Newspaper Guild: Out of Town Locals, 1957-1959 (Box 74, Folder 10)
  - American Newspaper Guild: Out of Town Locals, 1960-1962 (Box 74, Folder 11)
  - American Newspaper Guild: Out of Town Locals, 1963-1965 (Box 74, Folder 12)
  - American Newspaper Guild: Out of Town Locals, 1966-1969 (Box 74, Folder 13)
  - American Newspaper Guild: Out of Town Locals, 1970-1971 (Box 75, Folder 1)
  - American Newspaper Guild: Payroll Information, 1960-1962 (Box 75, Folder 2)
  - American Newspaper Guild: Pension Conference, 1957 (Box 75, Folder 3)
  - American Newspaper Guild: Pension Plans, 1962-1971 (Box 75, Folder 4)
  - American Newspaper Guild: Pension Plans Summary, 1960 (Box 75, Folder 5)
  - American Newspaper Guild: Per Capita, 1968-1971 (Box 75, Folder 6)
  - American Newspaper Guild: Photographers Conference, 1951 (Box 75, Folder 7)
  - American Newspaper Guild: Political Action Committee, 1950-1951 (Box 75, Folder 8)
  - American Newspaper Guild: Portland, 1961 (Box 75, Folder 9)
  - American Newspaper Guild Referendum: Elections, 1953-1955 (Box 75, Folder 10)
  - American Newspaper Guild Referendum: Elections, 1969 (Box 75, Folder 11)
  - American Newspaper Guild: Regional Weekend Institute, 1971-1972 (Box 75, Folder 12)
  - American Newspaper Guild: Staff Conference, 1953 (Box 75, Folder 13)
  - American Newspaper Guild: Strikes, 1953-1971 (Box 75, Folder 14)
  - American Newspaper Guild: Strike Committee, 1959-1961 (Box 75, Folder 15)
  - American Newspaper Guild: Strike Finance Committee, 1969-1970 (Box 75, Folder 16)
  - American Newspaper Guild: Strike or Lockout Benefits, General, 1970-1971 (Box 75, Folder 17)
  - American Newspaper Guild: Training Seminar, 1961 (Box 75, Folder 18)
  - American Newspaper Guild: U.S. Jobs for Veterans, 1971 (Box 75, Folder 19)
  - American Newspaper Guild: Wage-Price Bulletin, 1950-1951 (Box 75, Folder 20)
  - American Newspaper Guild: Washington Bureau, 1960 (Box 75, Folder 21)
  - American Newspaper Guild: Women's Rights Conference (I), 1970-1971 (Box 75, Folder 22)
  - American Newspaper Guild: Women's Rights Conference (II), 1970-1971 (Box 75, Folder 23)
  - American Red Cross, 1953-1961 (Box 75, Folder 24)
  - American Society of Magazine Photographers: Correspondence, 1946; 1957; 1960-1961 (Box 75, Folder 25)
  - American Telephone & Telegraph Company: Contract, 1952 (Box 75, Folder 26)
  - American Writers Conference, 1981 (Box 75, Folder 27)
  - Amnews Corporation and Newspaper Guild of New York (Arbitrations): Failure to Provide Health Insurance, 1981-1986 (Box 75, Folder 28)
  - Amnews Corporation and Newspaper Guild of New York (Arbitrations): Reduction of Salaries and Work Week, 1981-1986 (Box 75, Folder 29)
  - Amnews Corporation and Newspaper Guild of New York (Arbitrations): Failure to Pay Sales Bonuses, 1981-1986 (Box 75, Folder 30)
  - American Newspaper Publishers Association Research Institute, 1977 (Box 75, Folder 31)
  - Anti-Trust Activity (Radio, TV, etc), 1968 (Box 75, Folder 32)
  - Appeals Committee, 1957-1958 (Box 75, Folder 33)
  - Arbitrations Cases, 1951-1953 (Box 76, Folder 1)
  - Arbitrations Cases, 1954-1957 (Box 76, Folder 2)
  - Arbitrations Cases, 1958 (Box 76, Folder 3)
  - Arbitrations Cases, 1959 (Box 76, Folder 4)
  - Arbitrations Cases, 1960 (Box 76, Folder 5)
  - Arbitrations Cases, 1961 (Box 76, Folder 6)
  - Arbitrations Cases, 1962-1964 (Box 76, Folder 7)
  - Arbitrations Cases, 1965-1967 (Box 76, Folder 8)
  - Arbitrations Cases, 1968-1969 (Box 76, Folder 9)
  - Arbitrations Cases, 1970-1971 (Box 76, Folder 10)
  - Arbitrations Cases, 1972-1973 (Box 76, Folder 11)
  - Arbitrations Cases, 1974-1978 (Box 77, Folder 1)
  - Arbitrations Cases, 1979 (Box 77, Folder 2)
  - Arbitrations Cases (I), 1980 (Box 77, Folder 3)
  - Arbitrations Cases (II), 1980 (Box 77, Folder 4)
  - Arbitrations Cases, 1981-1982 (Box 77, Folder 5)
  - Arbitrations Cases, 1983-1990 (Box 77, Folder 6)
  - Arbitrations Cases: Jurisdiction, 1964-1970 (Box 77, Folder 7)
  - Arbitrations Cases: Jurisdiction, 1971-1975 (Box 77, Folder 8)
  - Arbitrations Cases: Jurisdiction, 1976 (Box 77, Folder 9)
  - Arbitrations Cases: Jurisdiction, 1977 (Box 77, Folder 10)
  - Arbitrations Cases: Jurisdiction, 1978-1979 (Box 77, Folder 11)
  - Arbitrations Cases: Jurisdiction, 1980-1987; undated (Box 77, Folder 12)
  - Arbitrations Cases: Other Unions, 1958-1964 (Box 77, Folder 13)
  - Arbitrations Award Index, 1958-1983 (Box 77, Folder 14)
  - Asbestos, 1986; 1989 (Box 77, Folder 15)
  - Associate Unit, 1951 (Box 77, Folder 16)
  - Associated Press Contracts, 1940-1944; 1954 (Box 77, Folder 17)
  - Astral Travel Service, 1961 (Box 77, Folder 18)
  - Attorney: In-House Subcommittee, 1975-1976 (Box 77, Folder 19)
  - Automate Headquarters, Ad Hoc Committee, 1979 (Box 77, Folder 20)
  - Automation, 1965-1991 (Box 77, Folder 21)
  - Australian Associated Press, 1964 (Box 77, Folder 22)
  - Bade: Wilber E. Bade Award, 1956-1963 (Box 78, Folder 1)
  - Baker, Ellis T. (Director of Administrative Operations): Correspondence, 1979-1981; 1984 (Box 78, Folder 2)
  - Baltimore Banner (interim paper during Baltimore Guild Strike), May 24, 1965 (Box 78, Folder 3)
  - Bargaining, 1950s (Box 78, Folder 4)
  - Bargaining (I), 1958 (Box 78, Folder 5)
  - Bargaining (II), 1958 (Box 78, Folder 6)
  - Bargaining, 1960s (Box 78, Folder 7)
  - Bargaining, 1970s (Box 78, Folder 8)
  - Bargaining, 1980s (Box 78, Folder 9)
  - Bargaining: Bell Syndicate, 1970-1971 (Box 78, Folder 10)
  - Bargaining: Citywide, 1951-1952 (Box 78, Folder 11)
  - Bargaining: Citywide, 1953-1955 (Box 78, Folder 12)
  - Bargaining: Citywide (I), 1956 (Box 78, Folder 13)
  - Bargaining: Citywide (II), 1956 (Box 78, Folder 14)
  - Bargaining: Citywide, 1960 (Box 78, Folder 15)
  - Bargaining: Citywide (I), 1962 (Box 78, Folder 16)
  - Bargaining: Citywide (II), 1962 (Box 78, Folder 17)
  - Bargaining: Citywide, 1963-1964 (Box 79, Folder 1)
  - Bargaining: Citywide, 1965 (Box 79, Folder 2)
  - Bargaining: Citywide, 1966-1968 (Box 79, Folder 3)
  - Bargaining: Citywide (I), 1969 (Box 79, Folder 4)
  - Bargaining: Citywide (II), 1969 (Box 79, Folder 5)
  - Bargaining: Citywide (I), 1970 (Box 79, Folder 6)
  - Bargaining: Citywide (II), 1970 (Box 79, Folder 7)
  - Bargaining: Citywide, 1971-1973 (Box 79, Folder 8)
  - Bargaining: Citywide, 1974-1976 (Box 79, Folder 9)
  - Bargaining: Citywide (I), 1977-1978 (Box 79, Folder 10)
  - Bargaining: Citywide (II), 1977-1978 (Box 79, Folder 11)
  - Bargaining: Citywide, 1980-1981 (Box 79, Folder 12)
  - Bargaining: Citywide Conference, 1967-1972 (Box 80, Folder 1)
  - Bargaining: Citywide Conference, 1975-1981 (Box 80, Folder 2)
  - Bargaining: Citywide (Ed Egan's complete files) (I), 1980-1981 (Box 80, Folder 3)
  - Bargaining: Citywide (Ed Egan's complete files) (II), 1980-1981 (Box 80, Folder 4)
  - Bargaining: Citywide (Ed Egan's complete files) (III), 1980-1981 (Box 80, Folder 5)
  - Bargaining: Citywide (Press coverage), 1977-1979 (Box 80, Folder 6)